junkrat primed and ready
don't suppose you'd like to trade fists
i mean
i don't think you could handle it
and i thought i'd taken my licks i was a
reckless youth
but you are something else entirely
hi champ why have you got that wombat
riding around with you
he is the pilot and i'm president of the
moon
seriously though what's he for please
move along
uh champ which of your glorious
victories
was your favorite the hamster is tired
of your questions
mine was when you big three i'm luke oh
you gave him the what for
where did you hide your treasure you
could hardly have it on your person
treasure
sure i don't know anything you're
talking about what's on your mind
mate i am thinking of what i have lost
watch your keys arrows snacks i've got
snacks
cheer up you look rich
you look like a man who inherited a vast
tribe of ostentatious wealth
i gave up my father's empire and his
fortune
alongside it
who has it now
but i'm a dozen actually
if he spent most of her adaway
foundation grant on me
it was not inexpensive
you look like the kind of guy who could
use something blown up
a candidate just came to mind
junkrat you're a reckless lunatic
oh thank you very much you got a problem
junker
i don't do problems just solutions
i heard there's a nice reward for
bringing you fellas in
maybe we could work something out mate
i get cold just looking at you then you
should look somewhere else
you're just no good bully how can you
even look at yourself in the mirror i
beg your pardon i consider myself a
freedom fighter
a misunderstood one you are
terrible that's cold
i hate bullies like you that's cold
you hook them i'll cook them oh shut
up you won't believe the jake old pig
face over there told me the other day
a roadhog do you ever shut up
try and stay out of trouble for once
i'll be on me best behavior
try not to get us killed out there
don't blow it when have i ever
uh don't answer that ah
remember that time we stole the crown
jewels
all hail king jameson forks the first
and uh duke roadhog what is your name
anyways
mako keep your stuff
off the table i'm hurt
i am nothing if not a courteous house
guest
you know i never would have taken you
for someone with such a homely
home if you don't like it stay in your
room
the queen sure seems to have an interest
in me
spy she fancies me i'd hate to break a
heart
[Music]
when i look at you i see pure
unadulterated chaos
is it the bombs you don't like the bombs
cheers mate the cavalry's here that's my
line
think i could have a look at one of
those bombs of yours over my dead
body
how many of you overwatch people are
missing an eye how many of you
scoundrels are missing a leg
hi jobs can we trade arms i don't think
they're compatible
and i thought i was supposed to be the
comic relief hey
was i serious guess we know who's really
on top
don't we never liked going to the doctor
four legs aren't better than one
turns out you actually did need healing
that time
too fast home field advantage you know
what do you think of that your majesty
there's no place like home
queen couldn't have done better herself
oh back to the scrap heap
i could always count on you mate i knew
there was a reason i kept you around
and it wasn't the sparkling conversation
that's why i'm paying you that 25
share that's what happens when you cross
junkrat
and roadhog hey i'm the only one who
gets to kill the big lug
thank you thank you thank you
where oh where is my pal road all gone
oh where oh where can he be